https://www.cmcs.com/privacy-policy

Home
Privacy Policy | CMCS, INC.
Privacy Policy
CMCS, INC. takes your privacy seriously.
Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy ("Privacy Policy"). This Privacy Policy applies to the use of the Sites (as defined below). Professionals, consumers and other persons using the Sites are individually and collectively referred to as "you", and CMCS, INC. and its subsidiaries and affiliates are referred to as, "CMCS, INC.", "we", "us" and "our". We use the Sites to provide you with information, resources, tools, products and services specific to the targeted industry and related markets, and to provide you with information about us and our advertisers, and our respective products and services.
CMCS, INC.is committed to implementing policies and procedures designed to protect your privacy and security, in addition to providing you with the best possible online experience. To that end, we want you to understand what kinds of information we gather about you, how this information is used and safeguarded, and how you can control its use.
In conjunction with this Privacy Policy, you should also review our Terms of Use for a complete understanding of the rules governing our Sites.
What information is collected from me?
Information You Give Us:
Information collected from you will vary, depending on how you use the Sites and what information you may choose to provide to us (whether through email or otherwise). It’s possible to browse most sections of the Sites without submitting any personally identifiable information. Personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") means individually identifiable information about you that we collect online, including but not limited to, your full name, a user name and password, email address, phone number, physical address, or, for certain products or services, your social security number, or financial information, and for certain e-commerce transactions your credit card information. If you choose to take advantage of some of our products and/or services, or to access certain of our tools or Site functionality, you may be asked to provide Personal Information. You can choose not to provide us with Personal Information, but then you may not be able to fully take advantage of certain features of our Sites and we may not be able to provide you with certain requested information, products and/or services.
Automatic Collection of Information:
Like many Web sites on the Internet, we automatically track certain information about you as you visit and use our Sites to help us to better understand how the Sites are used and how we can enhance your overall experience on each Site. This information may include your computer’s Internet Protocol address, the URLs and Site pages you’ve visited, the number of times you visit each Site page, what downloads and/or search queries you have made, how long you spent on particular sections of each Site and on each Site generally, and your browser type. This automatically gathered data includes information provided through the use of "cookies" (which is described in more detail below).
Information from Cookies:
Cookies are small files that we send to and store on your computer so that we can recognize it as a unique machine the next time you visit the Sites. You are always free to decline any cookies we use if your browser permits. Some of our advertisers and third-party service providers may also utilize their own cookies. Several of them may be part of the Network Advertising Initiative’s ("NAI") Self-Regulatory Principles Governing Online Preference Marketing. To opt out of the Premier Agent Networks Online Preference Marketing, every email sent has an opt-out option. In addition, we and our service providers sometimes use "clear GIFs" in connection with cookies and other website functions. Clear GIFs perform administrative functions without detracting from your online experience. They may be used to perform statistical and administrative tasks including measuring site and page traffic, verifying advertising avenues and positioning images on the web. Clear GIFs do not collect Personal Information.
Information Sharing Disclosure - How is my information used and shared?
The use of your information depends on the context in which it is collected. Therefore, pay special attention to the categories below that relate to the features of the Sites that you wish to utilize.
Personal Information
We may share the Personal Information we collect from you only with your consent or under the following circumstances: User-Requested Services and Information: Certain products or services on our Sites may seek Personal Information from you, which may be used in the following ways:
For products and services provided by the Sites, the information you submit is used by us to provide the information, product or service you’ve requested. We may also share this information with others, but only to the extent necessary to fulfill your request or to facilitate your use of their services. When sharing such information in such a manner, we may also share your Internet Protocol (IP) address. In addition, we may use any registration information that you submit as set forth in the "Registration Information" section below. We may use other companies and individuals toperform supporting functions for the various tools, functionality, products and services offered through our Sites on our behalf. These service providers will not be permitted to use the information collected from you for any other purpose other than performing the support functions for CMCS, INC..
For products and services offered to you jointly by us and a third party, your Personal Information may be shared with or independently gathered by the third party. In these situations, CMCS, INC. will only use your Personal Information as outlined in this Privacy Policy, but the third party may use the information in different ways. You can tell when a product or service is offered by a third party, because a page of the Sites will be "co-branded" and will display the third party’s logo and/or name along with our own, or you will be linked to the third party’s site to complete the transaction. Please be aware that each company we do business with has its own policies regarding the use and protection of your information that may differ from those outlined in this Privacy Policy.
User-Initiated Communication:
From time to time, portions of the Sites may enable you to send email to us or to third parties and to participate in public bulletin boards and discussion groups. All postings to public bulletin boards and discussion groups become our property. Your Internet Protocol (IP) address may be included in any email that you send, whether to us or to third parties. Whenever you choose to initiate these kinds of communication with us, or anyone else, you may be contacted in return. Also, remember that our bulletin boards and discussion groups are open to the public, and therefore, your postings can be seen by anyone and are not protected by us or any other entity. Please use your own discretion when deciding what to post and whom to contact. We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to edit or delete inappropriate postings from our bulletin boards and discussion groups. This reservation of rights shall not under any circumstances obligate us to conduct such edits or deletions, nor shall it cause us to be liable for any such edits or deletions.
Referrals: If you participate in any referral service we may offer:
Consumers:
We use the information you submit to determine which of our participating professional(s) may be able to serve your needs. We may then forward your information, which may include Personal Information, contained on our sign-up form to certain professional(s), who may then contact you.
Professionals:
You may receive information from consumers seeking your products or services, including, without limitation, their Personal Information. Because protecting consumer privacy is important, we require that you treat data received from Move consumers as if it was still on the Sites and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You may only use the information sent to you via our Sites for the purposes of providing products and/or services to the consumer. We require that you otherwise not share, use or transmit this information to or with any third party without the consumer’s consent.
Protection of rights:
We will release Personal Information if we believe that such action is appropriate to: (1) comply with legal process, (2) enforce the Terms of Use Agreement for the applicable Site, or (3) identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities who are or we believe will cause injury to us or a third party, or (4) otherwise protect the rights, property or personal safety of CMCS, INC., its employees, Site users or others.
Asset transfers:
We continue to develop our business and in doing so might choose to buy or sell other businesses or assets. Personal Information is generally one of the transferred assets acquired or transferred in such transactions.
Registration Information:
The Personal Information you provide when you become a registered user or customer of one of the Sites is used primarily to help us customize your online experience, increase the convenience of accessing new tools, products and services, and, if applicable, provide the products and/or services you purchase or request. This Personal Information may also be shared among the Sites to make your use of the Sites more convenient by, for example, limiting the number of times you have to register with us. Your email address serves as a unique identifier in our record system, and together with your password is designed to prevent unauthorized access to any information you choose to store on the Sites. The data you give us about your personal preferences and demographics (e.g., your age, ZIP code, occupation or the like) may be used to help us offer content, advertisements, products, and services that we believe will be of interest to you. In addition, we may share this information, in aggregate form, with our current and potential advertisers so that they can present advertisements more effectively. If you forget your password for any registered area of the Sites, we have an automated password recovery system, which can be accessed by clicking on the "Forgot Password?" link on the sign-in page.
Unless you specify that you’d prefer not to hear from us, we may use the email address you provide at the time of registration to contact you for promotional or other purposes. You may have these communications terminated at any time by opting out through your member profile on the applicable Site, or by clicking on any "unsubscribe" link contained in a promotional email. Please be aware that opting out on one of our Sites does not opt you out from any of our other Sites. If you would like to request to opt out with respect to all of the Sites please use our contact us page with your requests.
Professionals:
Personal Information provided to us from your trade association is not shared with third parties, unless you authorize it directly. We may offer a newsletter to keep you abreast of the products and services on the Sites or other professional products and services. Information such as your license number or personal financial information will not be shared with third parties except to complete a transaction or as provided in the paragraphs above. Additionally, information provided by you for the purposes of offering your products and services to others via one or more of the Sites will be shared with others, including consumers accessing one or more of the Sites. To the extent such information is necessary to offer such products and services it will be posted on the applicable Site(s). This may include, without limitation, your full name, email address, license number, state of license, address, phone number, graphic images and any other data intended to help consumers identify or contact you and for your products and services.
Non-personal Information
Automatically Gathered Information:
Information that is automatically gathered, including through the use of cookies, may be shared among the Sites and in aggregate form with other third parties, including listing providers, and advertisers, so that we may better understand how the Sites are used and to enhance your overall experience on the Sites. When such data is aggregated, all Personal Information is eliminated.
Children's Privacy:
Our Sites are general audience Web sites. If you are under the age of 13 you should not register or provide information on our Sites. We do not collect Personal Information from any person we actually know is a child under the age of 13. If you have knowledge that a child under the age of 13 has submitted Personal Information to us, please use our contact us page on this website.
Professionals:
You may edit your information by returning to the area of the Site where you registered and modifying the information there, or by contacting our Customer Care Center via the contact page on this website. By contacting Customer Care to make such changes, you expressly authorize Customer Care to access your data for the purposes of completing your requested edits, modifications and/or deletions.
How is my information protected?
Whenever Personal Information about you is stored on our computers, that information is password-protected from unauthorized access or use. In addition, this information is kept on servers that are located behind a firewall. Since your financial information and certain other Personal Information (i.e., your social security number) are especially sensitive, we take special care to keep it secure. We will only electronically transmit or ask for this information over secure Internet connections using SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption, the currently accepted standard for online security, and security keys. In addition, we require password authentication from any third parties you have authorized to receive this information. Finally, to the extent that we may ask for your social security number, credit card number or financial information, these will be stored on secure designated servers where access is limited to individuals in departments charged with using such information only in connection with processing your orders for products and services purchased; provided, however, that those orders processed by our partners, marketing allies and service providers that provide the service or product requested may store such information on their servers which are governed by such third party’s privacy policy and security procedures.
Of course, we appreciate your help in safeguarding the integrity of your own and others’ privacy. We hope you’ll use common sense whenever you disclose Personal Information over the Internet. Just as importantly, we encourage you to let us know immediately if you suspect that the information you share with us is being used in any way contrary to this Privacy Policy. Finally, unfortunately no data transmission over the Internet or the storage of information on servers can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and while we strive to protect your personal information, as described herein, we cannot guarantee or warrant its complete security. To contact us, please use our contact us form on this website.
Scope of This Privacy Policy: Outside Links
Be aware that our Sites link to other Web sites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. This Privacy Policy only applies to the Sites, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content for any linked Web sites. You should refer to the privacy policies and statements of other Web sites or contact the respective Webmasters of those Web sites to obtain information regarding their information collection, use and disclosure policies.
Effective Date and Modifications
This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date first written above and may be updated and modified from time to time by us in our sole discretion. If we choose to update or modify this Privacy Policy, such updated or modified policy shall become effective five (5) business days after its posting on the applicable Site(s). Accordingly, we encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy and the Sites in order to keep apprised of our current privacy practices. If you do not agree to any provision of this Privacy Policy, or any update or modification thereto, please do not use the Sites.
Contacting Us
If you have concerns about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices in general, contact us by using our contact us link on this website.
